WILLOUGHBY: It never begins.
And thus. it never ends.
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
(GUNSHOTS)
What's wrong?
Is that not all of it?
Too much of it.
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Garmen?
- Garmen?
- No. no.
- Not now. I told you...
- Every minute we do nothing.
we look weak. We
look confused. right?
The people. Our people.
The community. they're
looking for answers.
Cops. they're gonna
let this shit go.
- So what do we do?
- Aked. it's up to your auntie.
You know that. right? (STAMMERS)
She's not telling
me nothing. though.
Look. I love her. but this...
- It's family. It's my family.
- All right.
Ms. Mahabir. my condolences.
- I'm... I'm... I'm sorry. ma'am.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm going back home
for a few days.
Home to Georgetown?
Back to Guyana. Why?
To get some answers.
Auntie. we have all the answers.
Edward Chung killed
your brother-in-law.
Aked. this isn't
about Edward Chung.
This is about something that
happened a long. long time ago.
And I am going to
get some guidance
on exactly how to respond.
And believe me. I will respond.
And when I do.
I promise you'll be a part.
- A big part.
- A big part. I promise that.
"A long time ago." how?
(SIGHS) Yeah. I don't know.
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
WILLOUGHBY: You're right
to believe the bad things
happening to your family
are happening for a reason.
But I found the man responsible
for your misfortune.
and he's willing to allow you
to reverse your family's fate.
But you must be willing
to take certain steps.
exactly as he prescribes them.
- Are you willing?
- SAVITRI MAHABIR: I am.
You understand that to balance
the weight of his pain.
to close the circle
of his own suffering.
suffering which
began many years ago
at the hand of your
late husband. Ranwell.
you will have to
inflict a similar pain
on his behalf.
- SAVITRI: I know.
- Okay. then.
Here is where we begin.
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
SAMANTHA BROWNE: Jared.
honey. it's quarter of.
- I know.
- Is there anything I can do to help?
- 'Cause... (SIGHS)
- No. I'm coming.
You didn't touch
the avocado toast.
I don't want you getting
starved by second period
and eating from the
vending machine.
Mom. I ate earlier.
It was that Indian
food from last night.
- (SIGHS)
- Have you seen my cleats?
SAMANTHA: They're in the new
closet with the. uh. outside shoes.
DEREK BROWNE: I have to
say. I was kinda surprised
to see that pitch
meeting on the schedule.
We know we're gonna say no.
SAMANTHA: No. we
don't know that.
And anyway. sometimes knowing why
we're saying no can be good too.
Here's an idea.
how about your dad
actually takes one of
these meetings himself?
Oh? (SCOFFS) You mean do
the work part of work?
He did not eat that Indian food.
Okay. I'm putting your
food and a water...
Drink it... in your backpack.
Um. and bring home
the Tupperware. okay?
I'm picking you up
after school. bud.
- Don't run off.
- Dad. I know.
All right. if you're gonna
get the bus. we gotta move.
PRESENTER: We pay a
generous upfront fee
to license his
name and likeness.
and all we'd ask is
maybe once a year.
he gives us an
appearance or two.
Plus. Chef Jeff and his family
will always have a free room.
Whether it's Atlantic City...
Las Vegas...
or the big wow. Macau.
- Be in touch.
- Yeah.
See? It's good to do
sometimes. these meetings.
- Um. so. what...
- BRENDA: Jacket copy. blurbs.
and the publisher still needs you
guys to approve the cover image.
- Okay.
- And they wanna know.
is he keeping the ponytail?
I'm gonna let you handle that.
(SIGHS)
Hmm...
CAROL: Remember. all
you need to do is...
I know. I just...
I need to play nice
and don't interrupt.
Exactly. Just state your case.
'Cause it's a good
one. They need you.
They should have put
you on this a year ago.
Yeah. I would have
turned somebody by now.
Then my job wouldn't be
on the chopping block.
- So...
- So I know.
I need to just stay present.
not talk about the past.
I will be the model
of obedient servitude.
And he will never know how much I
think he's a backstabbing weasel
- who would sell out his own mother to...
- Mel. Mel.
- Nice face.
- (GROANS)
Right. Nice face.
MANNY BROWARD: Why don't you admit
why you really want on the case?
Pete Fong has to trim
the department budget.
you think you're vulnerable
'cause you're low man
on the pole. but...
we both know that's not the reason
why you're vulnerable. is it?
Maybe you actually really
don't wanna put me on the case
because it's stalling
and you know that
I would actually do
- something with it...
- (SCOFFS)
which would make you look bad
and then it would be
impossible for you to fire me
which is what you
really want to do
- if you're being honest. right?
- Well. if I'm being honest...
you're kind of impossible
to deal with. Mel.
I mean. case in point.
antagonizing your boss
as you're asking for a favor...
again.
Again?
Last year...
when I risked my fucking job
by not turning in
your psych eval?
- Remember that?
- (WHISPERS) Manny.
Yeah. Yeah. You asked real nice.
- Without fucking insults.
- (WHISPERS) Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry. And I get
it. You're right.
I appreciate it. okay?
But I don't want to
relitigate the past.
- I'm talking about my future.
- Hmm.
MELODY HARMONY: Which is me
working on the
Guyana case. okay?
- Not gonna happen. Mel.
- Manny!
Go back to the
Queen's College thing.
- Oh. my God!
- You were supposed to turn it in
- two weeks ago.
- Ugh! Right.
- Yes. You're right.
- Mm-hmm.
Because that massive
criminal organization
led by a dorm kid mailing fucking
fake IDs to high schoolers
is endangering more lives
than actual gangsters
murdering bums and vagrants
- for insurance premiums.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
Is the assignment not
sexy enough for you?
Here's a fact.
When you have a job.
you get assignments
from your boss. I'm your boss.
- (SIGHS)
MANNY: You don't do the
fucking assignment...
- Manny.
- You get fired.
Don't get fired. Mel.
Damn it.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(PHONE LINE RINGING)
CAROL: Well?
So I'm working the Guyana case.
Oh. my God! Well done.
you. So he agreed with you.
- Uh. no.
- CAROL: Uh. so...
So he didn't actually
put you on the case?
No. No. He didn't. No.
But you said you're
gonna work it.
Yeah. On my own time.
CAROL: Oh. Mel.
Yeah.
DEREK: Next one. Ready?
Here we go. Square up.
That's... not bad. Two hands.
Just watch it all
the way to the glove.
Here we go.
Here we go. Get it.
Get on your horse!
That was my bad. Good hustle.
Um. uh...
What? Seriously? He
lost his phone again?
You looked everywhere?
Behind the dugout?
- Yes. Dad.
- DEREK: Under the bench?
I said yes.
It was in my shoes.
Yup. He sure did.
- Really?
- You saw me take them off.
You saw me never go
back in the dugout.
I don't know how it happened.
DEREK: You heard correctly.
Yeah. we'll give him
the talk. Part Seven.
(SIGHS)
♪ (MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(CAR DOOR CLOSING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
♪ (MYSTERIOUS MUSIC FADES) ♪
♪ (SONG PLAYING OVER STEREO) ♪
- Hey.
- DEREK: Hey.
How'd it go with the
proofs? Pick a winner?
Oh. well. they're all winners.
So where did we land with
the whole losing stuff thing?
DEREK: I told him this
time there's no new one.
- You heard that. right. bud?
- JARED BROWNE: Yes.
Did you do Find My iPhone?
The phone has to
be on to track it.
I'm sure they wiped it anyways.
Are you sure?
'Cause you were
sure four months ago
when you lost the watch
that Grandpa Jeff gave you.
Grandpa's watch? You lost it?
W... How did I not know this?
And the sweatshirt.
His favorite one.
The one he waited in line for
then had to spend
four months allowance
to replace. Where are you going?
Find my iPhone. again.
Just tell me when
dinner's ready.
- I am not finished.
- Derek. just let him...
Moving forward. Jared.
buddy. help us out here.
Huh? What is the plan?
What kind of systems are
we gonna put in place.
so this all stops?
I don't know.
How about one where I don't
somehow lose everything?
(SIGHS)
I need two boys.
Preferably from GT.
GARMEN HARRY: What kind of time
frame are we talking. Ms. M?
As soon as possible.
GARMEN: Why Georgetown?
We probably got people here
who can do whatever you want.
No. Garmen. I want people
who will do what we say
and won't ask questions.
Natalia. the masseuse.
she have a brother who
got into trouble in GT.
He want to come up
with his best friend.
Let's arrange it.
- ♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(HORNS BLARING)
LOUIS WILLIAM: Yo!
- Xavier.
- Louis.
LOUIS: What's going
on? Look. look.
Now?
Bye. everybody. Bye.
- Ooh. Louis!
- LOUIS: Ooh!
(CHUCKLES)
- So this is really happen?
- LOUIS: Yeah. man.
You get the passport?
So when we at the forest
across the river...
- Raas. (CHUCKLES)
- they will give it to us...
- Uh-huh.
- Then take us to the airport.
Hey. Shakeela. It's me. Xavier.
Me buddy come through.
I know. I know.
I don't know. His sister
arrange everything.
Me and you. we go meet
in person. finally.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Ticketing.
They not gonna see us for a
very. very. very long time.
- Long time. Long time.
- (XAVIER LAUGHS)
Let's go.
(CHUCKLES)
LOUIS: Kingston to
Georgetown. brother.
XAVIER: Yeah. man.
And now New York!
Yeah. yeah. yeah! New York!
- Yeah. man.
- Crazy.
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC FADES) ♪
Hey. hey. Shakeela.
It's me. Xavier.
I can't wait to
see you in person.
We got a little meeting
first. but let me know
what time school finish and. uh.
text me a place you want meet.
(CHUCKLES)
Louis. your sister
waiting for you.
She'll take you both straight
to your meeting with Aked.
Little gift to get you started.
Thank you. Mr. Len.
- XAVIER: Thank you. sir.
- Thank Mrs. Mahabir.
It's from her.
Oh. and I need your passports.
Um. okay.
- LOUIS: Hey. Xav.
- XAVIER: Mm-hmm.
Let me be straight with you.
Us coming here wasn't
my sister's idea.
You told me she
arrange everything.
LOUIS: No. Natalia boss
My sister may not be
too happy to see us.
Just warning you.
And you're just
telling me this now?
Yeah.
(HORN BLARING)
I hear you was
running weed. Louis.
which means you lied
to me on the phone.
We was just tricked. Nat.
Point was I gonna be
sending you money this time.
Point is. I hope you happy
'cause now you into
something different.
Ain't even a hello? Hey!
You'll get one when
I'm done being mad.
(CLICKS TONGUE. SIGHS)
This... this Xavier.
Friend I tell you about.
He from up river too.
My sister. Natalia.
Me auntie friends
with your mother.
Oh. I know you.
In our primary school
you stole my kickball.
Probably. I don't know.
Well. Xavier. you got
legs. You can follow too.
Let's go. You coming or not?
Now ain't the time
to keep Aked waiting.
AKED: The thing
about Garmen Harry.
Number one. loyalty.
Number two.
loyalty.
And number three...
What's number three? What was...
Oh. loyalty. (CHUCKLES)
All right?
Is Garmen the boss?
Garmen "Mr. Harry" to you.
The boss is Mrs. Mahabir.
Or if and only if she gives
you permission. Ms. M.
Full disclosure.
Savitri Mahabir is my aunt.
So you wanna talk
to her? Through me.
Ask Nat.
I don't do this
for nobody. Nobody.
But she vouches for
you. baby brother.
You...
I don't know about.
But what you say is
true they gonna use you.
How much they pay?
Place to stay. lawyers
for a Green Card.
and you must be forgetting
they paid for your travel.
but I'm gonna let that slide.
You work it off.
- Sky the limit.
- How much I work off?
AKED: About 50K per.
something like that.
U.S.?
(COUGHS. CHUCKLES)
U.S.? I like this
guy. You funny.
Yeah. yeah. U.S.
We're here now. baby.
Mm-hmm.
Sometime few weeks from now.
a guy. Paul. is gonna
assign you a trial.
Savitri Mahabir. Garmen Harry.
Paul Tranquada. me...
you.
(HORN BLARING)
(LOUIS EXHALES)
You guys are good?
Yeah? You know
what you're doing?
All right. You can't miss him.
He's in a wheelchair. If
he's awake. he's talking.
I hope you boys appreciate the
nature of this opportunity.
- Yes. sir.
- Yeah?
- Thank you. sir.
- Yeah.
- Thank you. Mr. Paul. sir.
- You're welcome.
All right. You guys can go.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(LAPTOP CHIMES)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC FADES) ♪
NEILSEN: No. no. no. no. man.
The plastic is in the atmosphere
'cause the damn astronauts
keep throwing the shit
out the window. I mean.
we... we got plastic
in our blood now.
'Cause of NASA.
Yeah. yeah. It's in a book.
I... I read all the books.
I read 'em all. You see?
The books are the truth.
I know that the only way
you can tell the truth
is to put it in a book.
And everybody else knows
that. You see what I'm saying?
Oh. how do you know that?
Because ink cost money.
Fucking wasting my time
around stupid-ass shit.
I'm a book reader. I read
books. That's what I do.
They mad at me
because I know stuff.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Hey. brother. we get
something for you.
Yo. what the... The fuck?
Yo. who... who are you. man?
Quiet down. man.
Yo. what you doing? No.
no. I'm good. I'm good.
- Relax yourself.
- You can stop here. I'm good.
I just get a little
present for you.
Yo. who are you with. man?
- Are you with Paul?
- Just a friend. All right?
- No. no. no. I'm asking. Wait.
- XAVIER: Keep your voice down.
- Shut your mouth.
- NEILSEN: What are you doing. man?
What are you... No. stop.
How you... No. no. no.
No. no. No. no. I don't
want nothing. I'm clean.
- It's gonna be all right.
- No. I swear. I'm good. man.
I'm good. No. I'm
sorry. (GRUNTS)
Come on. please. No.
What are you doing?
- Come on! Move! Help me. man.
- NEILSEN: No. no. please. Stop.
- Help. man!
- Hey. man. Help me. man.
- Come on. (YELLS. CHOKES)
- XAVIER: Quiet. man. Relax yourself.
Quiet yourself. Sorry.
Move. Move now. man.
LOUIS: Natalia. Did you
know they would do that?
You did know?
They make it look
like an accident.
But it ain't no accident.
He raas did know.
Nat. That scunt.
NATALIA WILLIAM: I've been
trying to get out. Louis.
- LOUIS: Shit.
- I been trying.
- LOUIS: Oh. shit.
- ♪ (TENSE MUSIC FADES) ♪
NATALIA: I'm at massage
school two nights a week.
I got janitorial at
the message school
five nights a week.
I got Ms. Mahabir
during the day.
so I can pay her off.
Almost done too.
Every time one of
them dead. Natalia.
you are part of it.
- (EXHALING)
- (DOOR CLOSING)
SAVITRI: The new boys were the
ones that pull it off with Neilsen?
GARMEN: The two of them. One...
one better than the other.
but with Neilsen's drug history.
they could pass this
one through fast.
We anticipating a payout
for the full policy.
Three hundred and
twenty-five thousand dollars.
Ooh! That's good. Well done.
Uh. but that not
come until next year.
We got some bigger
issues this year.
especially when I trying
to... (SIGHS) ...reconcile
the financial mess
Quincy left us in
- after he died...
- SAVITRI: Look. Garmen. Garmen.
Let's focus forward.
You mean. uh. for this
next thing you get?
Whatever it is.
- Coming down the pike.
- That one. Yes.
(SCOFFS) Well. how am I gonna know
unless you tell me what that thing is.
It's the most important
thing we've ever done.
It involves a boy.
But I don't want to say no more
because me nah wan
blight de ting.
So you're scared me will jinx
it and give you a bad eye.
but I can't run it
unless you tell me...
(CHUCKLING) ...what it is.
SAVITRI: You're not
gonna run it. Aked is.
(LAUGHS) Ma'am.
You say it's the
most important thing.
It's also the most dangerous.
And this way you can supervise.
stay safe and help Aked.
Try not to kill himself.
AKED: Natalia. I told you
this was gonna be big.
This is huge. So
what's your problem?
NATALIA: Why is kidnapping
some pickney gonna make up
for what happened to Quincy?
- AKED: Reasons.
- NATALIA: Reasons?
- Yes. Reasons.
- NATALIA: Aked.
From the boss.
Who's grieving right
now. You know that.
Look. my auntie
left me in charge.
All right? Me in charge of
all this. You understand?
Version six.
I like this one.
Leave notes. Okay?
So you know. like. um.
Chef Jeff or whoever. the
kid's father. whatever.
They pull up to the
library. boom. next place.
Subway station. I don't
know. I'm making it up.
Boom. They get to the
library. open up an envelope.
"Congratulations. you
made it to the library.
Now you got to book
it to the bridge."
Gonna keep it clever.
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
XAVIER: So yeah. Yeah.
Shakeela. It's me. Xavier.
So yeah. I was thinking
maybe we could do that again.
Maybe nighttime this time.
Or. you know.
maybe even tonight?
I just going for a walk now. so
if you done all your homework
and you feel like
catching a vibe just. uh.
yeah. just give me a call.
But. um...
Yeah. I'ma call you right back.
You didn't happen
to be in the alley
behind Gemini's Lounge
the other night. did you?
Is. um.
this familiar to you? You
know. dead body. wheelchair.
We brought the sheet.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- No idea.
- Oh. you know. I wonder
if I described the alley to
you. if it will jog your memory.
So we have Gemini's Lounge.
next to the laundromat.
next to the pawn shop.
which. like all pawn shops.
has a security camera
which as you know.
have gotten very
good these days.
- Let me see that.
- Oh. I... Sorry.
It's government
property. (CHUCKLES)
However. my name is on this.
And whenever you're ready to
give me yours. give me a call?
(SIGHS)
CLARENCE JOSEPH: It will happen
in Washington Square Park
at 1:11 a.m.. inside a circle.
We will be in the park
to make sure there is no
deviation from the plan.
He will feel the same pain I
felt when I lost my grandson.
- ♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC FADES) ♪
- A boy for a boy.
And the balance will be
restored and all will be good.
It will.
Well. uh. I want to hear
from Mr. Joseph directly.
Everything will be good.
SAVITRI: Excellent. excellent.
Thank you. gentleman.
CLARENCE: Thank you.
It was an honor. madam.
SAVITRI: Oh. the honor was
all mine. I assure you.
WILLOUGHBY: We'll see you
tomorrow night at the celebration.
SAVITRI: Yes. Tomorrow
we shall celebrate.
- I'll be right there. Natalia.
- Yes. Ms. Mahabir.
Natalia. is
everything all right?
- Yes. Ms. Mahabir.
- Hmm.
(COUGHS)
- Good night. sir.
- Good night.
Xavier. I need you to go
to Washington Square Park.
Lower Manhattan.
You can Google it.
Ms. Mahabir asking
for... for. um...
um... (CHUCKLES)
Apparently. there are...
circles in the park
in different places.
She want to know the various
sizes. where. how many...
Yeah. My advice to you. Xavier.
watch your ass on this one.
Good night. sir.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SIGHS) Okay.
I just don't feel like
four people talking in a room
for two hours is a movie.
Okay. I just
thought you'd be mad
that I brought you to a
movie where you had to read.
Yeah. I mean. that didn't help.
- (LAUGHS)
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh. shit. Hold on.
Uh. Inspector Harmony
speaking. Who might this be?
XAVIER: My name is Xavier.
If I give you information.
can you get me home?
Home. home. home? Like Guyana?
- XAVIER: Yes.
- No.
But I can try to
make your life easier
in direct proportion to
the information given.
Divided by. of course. how
seriously you've already
fucked your life.
XAVIER: Something is
going down tomorrow night.
MELODY: Well. that's
a good first step.
Second step. where
is it happening?
Washington Square Park.
It's four in the morning.
Why are you waking me up?
They gonna kill that boy.
The one they kidnapping. I
heard Mrs. Mahabir say it.
No matter what happen.
she want to kill him.
Why?
She think it some kind of answer
to all the bad that's
been happening.
- How that make sense?
- She crazy is how.
All of sudden. nothing
she do makes sense.
She bring these people
here from Guyana last week
and got a whole plan.
And he picked
Xavier for the plan.
but I just told him you'd be good too
because we need one more person...
- You put me up for that?
- Quiet!
You're all upset about it
then you put me up for it?
- This is exactly what I don't want to do.
- I got a plan. Louis!
You ain't gonna kidnap the boy.
You're gonna save him.
We gonna.
What?
- Why?
- Because you said it...
If someone dead.
I'm a part of it.
I'm trying to do
the right thing.
And you should be too.
LOUIS: Natalia. Natalia!
The thing that's happening...
when that gonna happen?
Aked was worried if he put
a crew together too soon.
they'd talk so we just
know telling Xavier...
Natalia. When this a happening?
Tonight.
Muddaskunt.
Tonight? And you're just
telling me this now?
I had to wait 'till
Aked fell asleep.
I don't know how we
gonna do all of it.
gonna do most of it.
But I know how we
at least can start.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (TENSE MUSIC FADES) ♪
I'm texting you where
to go to get the bike.
It's got to be the exact
laundry bike that Aked is using.
You see the photo here. Okay?
And I need you to
get this black bag.
I'm texting it now to you. Okay?
And get a wig. Any
type of wig. Okay.
Now. I'm sending you a address
I need you to leave the bike.
I go get it after work. I
go put the dummy inside.
All right? I need you to text me
when you get close to
the park. All right?
So which one of my
plans we going with?
The one where you wait for
us to tell you what to do.
- When is that?
- When we tell you.
JARED: They've gotten
super controlling.
They won't even let
me lock my phone.
They're trying to prove a point
about me being responsible.
Plus. I can't go out
anyway. I've got tutor.
What if I promise
it'll be worth it?
Like... I can tell you what
happened to your stuff.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
AKED: It's a
business transaction.
I'll tell you more about it
in the van. Okay? Come on.
LOUIS: How is grabbing a little
boy a business transaction?
AKED: I said I'd tell you
more about it in the van.
You good. Louis?
What's good with you?
Your sister said you
could handle this.
I got to set her straight?
So come on.
Keesen!
Let's go. Come on.
(DOOR OPENING)
XAVIER: Me will come just
now. Let me grab something.
(EXHALES)
MELODY: So what do you got?
Yeah. so Agent
Lady. I was wrong.
Ain't nothing happening
tonight. I was wrong.
MELODY: What do you mean
nothing's happening?
I messed up and I'm sorry.
- And I can't do this.
- MELODY: What? Xavier. no.
- you can't just back out like this.
- I'm sorry. Agent Harmony...
- MELODY: Xavier. you cannot...
- Hey!
You ready?
Me good.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC FADES) ♪
Was that your guy?
Yeah. It was Xavier.
He said that Washington Square
Park isn't happening tonight.
but it obviously is.
(SIGHS) I just... Give me a sec.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Hey. Manny. um...
Listen. I know you're with
your daughter tonight.
so I hope you even get this.
Uh. I also hope
you actually think
that this is good news. but
I did go a little rogue.
And it was on my own
time. so don't worry.
but I actually did manage to turn
a cooperator... (SIGHS) ...ish.
And that he said that there
was something happening
in Washington
Square Park tonight.
But then he said there isn't.
Which makes me think
that there is. (CHUCKLES)
And that it's bigger than
the whack-a-bum stuff
because why would they
be killing a vagrant
in Washington Square Park.
so I feel like I should
definitely be there.
but I don't want to go
until I hear back from you
because I am trying to be
professional and to respect protocol.
So. um. yeah. when you get
this. just. uh. hit me back
and. um. yeah. I'll
be sitting tight.
Okay. Bye.
So are you gonna
wait for his approval
- or...
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Right.
KRISTIN MCCUSKER: Hey. Jared?
- Jared?
- JARED: Yeah.
KRISTIN: The microwave's
jammed. The door won't open.
Oh. the microwave. Yeah.
Yeah. It's not jammed.
It's a drawer now.
Yeah. You know. it's
this... This whole thing.
There's a button.
Oh. my God.
Since your parents remodeled.
I can't figure out a damn thing
in this place. Are you
sure you're not hungry?
No. I'm... I'm not
feeling too good.
I'm just gonna crash tonight.
Well. don't you have tutor?
Uh. I think I'm
just gonna cancel.
- Mm-hmm.
- If I'm sick.
I don't want to get Sarah sick.
So... yeah.
Did you call her?
Oh. I actually lost my phone.
Do you think you
could call her for me?
Mom left her number on the
sheet next to the phone.
You do look a little flushed.
Okay. sweetie. I will.
- Thanks. Nanna.
- Can I get you some soup?
No. I'm just gonna go to bed.
- I'm not really hungry.
- All right.
- Well. hope you feel better.
- JARED: Yeah.
KRISTIN: (CLICKS TONGUE)
Oh. sweetheart. Love you.
JARED: Love you too.
Good night. Nanna.
KRISTIN: Good night.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- AKED: Do you see her right there?
- LOUIS: Mm-hmm.
That's the tutor girl.
She gonna come. she gonna
post up on the building.
check her phone.
It's maybe Instagram or
something. I don't know.
But she waits. she
might call him. Hold on.
She ready. then they
gonna go across the park
right now and go to the Bean.
Do some school shit.
As soon she leaves with him.
that's when we go. okay?
What the fuck?
What the fuck!
Yo. I told Len to track him
the last two fucking Saturdays.
Wait. I got a backup.
I got these FedEx
joints. maybe we go.
- we knock on the door...
- XAVIER: Hey. Aked.
That him? Right
there. that door?
Yeah. that's him.
That's him. Where is he going? Where
is this motherfucker going? What?
That's a one-way. He
just went up a one-way.
Fuck. Go up. um. next block.
Next block. Make a right.
I don't see shit.
Thought you said this man
was already there. chief?
No. I know. I know.
Okay. this right. right here.
You take this right. right here.
Right here.
I just can't take anything
he says seriously.
All I can do is picture him sitting
in that chair with tin foil on...
- (LAUGHS)
- ♪ (TENSE MUSIC FADES) ♪
Oh. that's not fair.
Not everyone can rock
- the silver fox like you.
- Oh. God bless you.
- but you know what I mean.
- Hey. Mom.
Um. hey. thanks
for the heads up.
Yeah. Well. I hope
you don't mind
- the executive decision.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah. No. I mean.
no sense doing
tutor if he's sick.
- Um. night.
- KRISTIN: Night. night.
- DEREK: Good night. Kris.
- KRISTIN: Good night. Derek.
(DOOR CLOSING)
SAMANTHA: Aw.
DEREK: I think he just
didn't wanna do tutor.
(SAMANTHA LAUGHS)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
All right. Fuck it. Take
this left right here.
Right here. Right here.
- Right here?
- Yeah.
- Nothing?
- Mm-mm.
(AKED EXHALES SHARPLY)
Fuck it. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
Wait. wait. wait. There's
he. There's he. Right there!
- Yeah. Yes! Yeah. Keesen!
- (CHUCKLES)
Go. go. go. go. Xavier.
Hurry. hurry. hurry.
(TAP RUNNING)
(TAP TURNS OFF)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC FADES) ♪
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hi. Thank you. You must
have my son's phone.
He's always losing his stuff.
AKED: Actually.
we have your son.
- SAMANTHA: What?
- AKED: I said we have your son.
And we'll kill him if
you don't do what we say.
- SAMANTHA: Hang on. Hang on. Hang on.
- AKED: All right? Yo. lady.
- you're not in charge here.
- SAMANTHA: No. I said hang on!
AKED: You need to stop talking
- and start listening...
- DEREK: Sam?
AKED: or this will be the worst
night of your life. You hear me?
- DEREK: What's going on?
- (BREATHES HEAVILY)
- They have Jared.
- What?
AKED: Damn right. we do. And
here what's gonna happen...
Whoa. whoa. whoa. If this is a
joke. it's not funny. Who's talking?
AKED: I'm gonna
give you a figure.
and I suggest you write it down.
Do you have Jared? I
want to talk to Jared.
Who is this? Who is
talking to me right now?
AKED: Three hundred and fourteen
thousand. one hundred and fifty-nine.
- Write that number down. It's important.
- Wait. wait. wait. Just... wait.
- What are these numbers?
- SAMANTHA: Three. one. four. one...
- This is... this is money?
- Derek. shh!
No. you need to
tell us something.
Give us some information.
AKED: White sneakers.
there's writing on them.
(NICKY GROANS)
AKED: Yellow and green
Trek mountain bike.
You're gonna get a call shortly
explaining where you pick
up the money. All right?
- (NICKY GROANS)
- Yes. cash.
Nothing bigger than
twenties. you hear me?
Man. I don't know. Why don't you
ask your fucking father-in-law
what his Atlantic City
credit limit is. All right?
(CLICKS TONGUE) You sure
about that move. Clarence?
You might want to rethink that.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Again. Sorry. Sorry.
Of course.
Sam. I am playing
chess with my friend...
Just... Sam. Slow down.
Slow down. Slow down!
What?
What!
Uh. uh. I'm sorry.
I... I... I...
I've got to go.
Uh. I'll. uh. I'll...
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
JEFFREY MCCUSKER: Just
tell him it's an emergency.
I need to borrow
against my credit limit!
Because I can't right now. Joey!
Did she tell you anything?
I... I know about
as much as you do.
Look. just call Sey. If
he's not on the casino floor
- then he's gonna be awake somewhere.
- Oh. Chef Jeff. Ms. McCusker.
- you forgot to sign...
- Not now. Bryce.
Yes. Just do it.
Call me back.
- (BREATHES DEEPLY)
- (WHIMPERS)
- KRISTIN: My God. Oh. my God.
- JEFF: Sam. Anybody called?
Derek?
Joey called my guy
in Atlantic City.
DEREK: They haven't
told us a thing.
You know. I'm sorry
you're involved.
What... what are
you apologizing for?
Did you fucking do
it? Don't apologize.
- Wait. Joey?
- Wait. Dad! He said no police.
- Joey's not police. He's not anymore.
- I checked and he was there.
- Honest to God!
- He's the best there is.
- I checked and he was there.
- Kris!
- Yes?
- This is not about you.
- I know that. but I...
- Can we just take a beat?
- I looked in his room...
- We don't have a fucking beat.
- And he was there... (SOBS)
- This is a nightmare.
- Kris.
- I would never... What?
Kristen. it's not you.
- We're not mad at you.
- No. no. no. no. no. no.
- Mom! Mom!
- I'm fine. I'm fine. (SOBS)
- SAMANTHA: Hey. Hey. hey.
- (KRISTIN SOBS)
- Oh. my God.
- (JEFF GROANS)
I... I... can't. Um. okay. wait.
- So police. Yes or no?
- Joey says...
not until Jared's safe at home.
And who the fuck knows about
my casino credit limit?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Yes?
- AKED: Okay. listen to me.
There's a parking lot right
next to the south entrance
of the George Washington
Bridge. All right?
Tell your boys at the casino
to drop your cash there.
When you're on the
bridge with the money.
you'll receive your next
instruction. all right?
Look. if you're not
there by midnight.
if you're not alone or
police have been called.
your son will be killed.
Okay. put our son on
the phone. please.
- (LINE DROPS)
- (SIGHS)
Fuck. (BREATHES DEEPLY)
- KRISTIN: Jared.
- What the fuck?
Jared? Oh. my God.
Where have you been?
Jeez. Mom. I just
went out for a walk.
- Calm down. What...
- Sweetheart.
DEREK: You lied to
your grandmother.
Derek. he's here.
Derek. it's fine.
No. no. no. no. no. no.
He was sneaking. He
lied to your mom and us.
I didn't realize
how late it was.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm so glad. I just...
- SAMANTHA: Please. Please.
- JARED: Calm down.
SAMANTHA: Just be
honest with us. Okay?
Were you... were
you meeting someone?
A boy? A girl? It
doesn't matter.
- Just... just talk to us. Please.
- JEFF: This is not the time
to be fucking around. son.
This is not the time
to be fucking around.
This is no time to fuck around.
This is not... Hold
on. Just hold on.
- (DOOR CLOSING)
- (SAMANTHA EXHALES)
DEREK: Hey. you need to talk
to us. bud. What's going on?
SAMANTHA: Okay. y... y...
you're not in trouble.
but this is important.
DEREK: Jared.
There's this boy
I've been talking to.
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
He said he had all my stuff.
And he'd show it to me
if I went to go see him.
So I lied to Nanna
and I snuck out.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
When I got there he
was wearing my hoodie.
My original one from
before I replaced it.
And he had my shoes too.
He really liked my bike.
so I let him ride it
around a little bit.
But then a van came.
these guys jumped out
and they threw him in.
And I couldn't do
anything about it.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
I just got my bike
and I rode around
until I could work up the
nerve to come back home.
Oh. baby.
Oh. my God. That had
to have been horrible.
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC FADES) ♪
- I think they were after me.
- Why would you think that?
If it had been two minutes
earlier. they would have gotten me.
Oh. baby.
JARED: Why would
somebody be after me?
We don't know.
We don't know anything. bud.
What do you know about
this boy? What's his name?
His name is Nicky.
Look. is he gonna be okay?
Open it. Open it. Open
it right now. Open it.
Yeah. Come here. Come here.
Come here. Look at me.
Look at me. You know
how to take pills?
Did boss send you old man
gummy bear sleeping pills?
Shut the fuck up. I'm
not talking to you.
Jared. do you know
how to take pills?
Don't fuck with
me. Look at these.
You know how to take these? Huh?
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Ruby. Here we go.
You're okay. You're good. Okay.
- Hey. Joey.
- Sam. Hello.
Hey. so the casino asked why
so much cash so quickly...
JEFF: So you... you
can cancel all that.
DEREK: He's here.
Jared. He's in his room.
- Hey. Joey.
- How you doing. Mr. Browne?
- He's... Jared's here?
- JEFF: Mm.
- Well. that's good. Right?
- KRISTIN: Oh. yeah.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (DEREK SIGHS)
Well. the place looks good. Wow.
Don't even recognize it.
- (SAMANTHA SIGHS)
- (DEREK GRUNTS)
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- What? What?
- Who is this?
- Derek.
Please. Who am I talking to?
NICKY: Daddy? Dad?
- Who... who is this?
- AKED: Is there a problem?
N... no. sir.
There's no problem.
We just need to gather
some information.
Gather some information?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Gather some... What the
fuck are you talking...
Hello?
They're muting me?
Bolt cutters.
- Huh?
- Give me the bolt cutters.
Give me the fucking
bolt cutters.
Come here. Xavier. pull
over. Pull the fuck over.
Aked. what are you doing. buddy?
AKED: Record this right
now. Hurry. Hurry.
(NICKY SCREAMING)
No. I do not negotiate
with a terrorist.
- Jeff. come on. They have someone's child.
- SAMANTHA: Okay. okay.
- So now... now we call the police. Right?
- I don't... I don't know.
Do we call the police. Joey?
- (CELL PHONE CHIMES)
- Wait. is that them?
DEREK: Yeah. There's
a video attached.
SAMANTHA: Play it.
- (NICKY GRUNTING. SCREAMING)
- (GASPS)
- Oh. Holy Christ.
- Oh. my God!
AKED: Hold still. You're
making it worse. Jared.
- (NICKY SCREAMING IN PAIN)
- KRISTIN: Oh. Jesus Christ.
Oh. my God!
They think... they
think they have Jared.
- But they don't.
- Yeah. but if they find out they don't.
what's to keep them
from coming after him?
JEFF: Well. what do we do?
Do we just pretend that...
That it's Jared or what?
- ♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
NICKY: (SOBBING) It hurts.
Please do what they say.
JEFF: We just need
a few more details.
Jared. I want you to
talk about yourself.
NICKY: Call... Charisse.
AKED: We'll talk at midnight.
If you're on a bridge
and if you're alone.
Wait. What... what
do you mean "alone?"
AKED: One person. No cops.
Oh. and if I don't have the
money by 1:11 a.m. sharp.
your boy. your
grandson. Chef Jeff.
is dead.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC
INTENSIFIES. FADES) ♪
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC FADES) ♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-